The Gayest Side of The Great White Way
Broadway Nights is a drama, romance film directed by Joseph C. Boyle.
Fannie joins Johnny to perform a music-hall act which becomes a success, until two Broadway producers catch the act and offer
Fannie a job on their latest show; however, they have no place for Johnny, so Fannie turns down the offer.
(Film considered lost.)
Fanny Franchette, played by Lois Wilson.
Johnny Fay, played by Sam Hardy.
Baron, played by Louis John Bartels.
Bronson, played by Philip Strange.
Texas Guinan, played by De Sacia Mooers.
Performer, played by Georgette Duval.
Broadway Nights is a lost 1927 American silent
romantic drama film directed by Joseph C.
It was the film debut of June Collyer, Barbara
Stanwyck, Sylvia Sidney and Ann Sothern.
The film explores themes of silent film, music hall, lost film.
The tone is emotional.